I promised to answer questions.
We'll do a few questions, and then move on to the
smaller ones.
I have a question;
it's a technical question. It's a
technical question, like a comeback. I'm
afraid someone will ask me something you ca
n't answer.
If we plant seeds, these farms
double every 24 hours,
then we have many, many seeds, and they
open 65 times per second, with
this small, radiant light
coming out of the seed. At what point is the seed the tree, instead of having
millions of oak trees?
Many of the questions you have aren't in
the scriptures,
but I can give a few hints.
When the image comes out of the seed, like
when a tree grows from the seed, the tame one is
destroyed by it.
When the image comes out and
lies on the subject, at the moment the
image reaches the object, I would say
something disturbed, and the tree and the image
are the tree.
I'm not telling you more because I don't
know exactly what you're supposed to answer to a question.
In Buddhism,
every result is also...  One cause
is the second way seeds
open, so the second flower comes from the fact
that he will also discuss this week
that when the money comes and you are
aware that it will be a picture,
it will plant another seed, and
then we harvest a habit. If you
commit to a camera once, and a way in which the
camera develops, how did life come about? This is
a habit.
Perhaps it will be easier for you if you
think about watermelons. You can have
a seed, the watermelon info
result, and in the watermelon there are
hundreds of seeds again, and each
seed can produce a watermelon, and
each of these watermelons has
500 together. And
that helps you understand how
seeds multiply, and the third
flower, its seeds create your environment.
So if you like to consume drugs or alcohol,
when you drink, you plan
a name,
and when the seed opens it, then you create
people around you
who find the same pleasure,
and then they encourage you to drink even more,
and then it's a cycle.
But that's the picture that  It comes out
having no permanence, not like a
big tree.
Michael, you always teach such great
things. We really like it when you're
here. Many thoughts I
have in my mind I don't like.
I think clearly about taking refuge. I
can live in the spirit of a brother. Could you please teach
us how to take refuge in this way
so that we don't have to have these
negative thoughts that
we have? For many years I was the translator for
my lama. He spoke English
and I translated it into English.
I sat next to him, and when
he had private interviews with people,
they would ask him a question,
and then he would answer,
and then we would say what. And then
I did that myself, and then
they sometimes told me that I had
translated. I actually did. So anyway, once
I remember
they came to him, and I was at the
door, and then they
asked me if we could come in.
I built his house
[music].
And before we lived there, we
drew a plan on packages. It was
a two-story house, and next to it was another
house.  And then he said we'll do
the entrance doors here and I'll
stay upstairs on the second floor and you'll
stand down there, and then people have to go past you to get to
me,
and then I could
never really hit him, and then once a
woman came who said I have to talk to the llama,
I'm depressed, depressed all the time,
and then I thought, yes,
she really should talk to the llama,
and then we went upstairs
and talked to the llama,
and then he said, I'm very sad, I
'm very depressed, depressed all day
long, I'm depressed, what should
I do?
And then my long gender didn't even say that,
and then I looked at him and he looked at her and
how he looked at her,
and then he said again he was
just happy,
and then he said, so see you soon, and then I
thought, and then sometimes I went upstairs
to him afterward, went into the
room, and then I went upstairs and
then I asked him
what kind of answer that was,
expected the perfect answer,
then he caught up with me, I
'm your llama, the perfect answer,
but in America, llama, that's not  Such
a good answer,
and then he said that it's simply too
late to be unhappy
when you're depressed, when the seeds
sprout in your head, or warm thoughts that you don't like,
for example, when someone
annoys you and the thought goes from one
side to the other, and then no, no, so
a strange thought, when it
comes into your mind, similarly
opens up, then it's too late to
push the tree back into the ground.
They say that the light comes from the
stars, from the stars, and one of the
stars we see doesn't even exist anymore,
but the light hasn't reached us yet,
and it's the same with our mind.
When you hear the thought, then
the warm thought has already opened me. It
takes just a tiny second for the
thought to reach your ear.
So if you're already depressed, then
it's too late
not to be depressed
today. But of course, you can
plant a warm thought today for next
week. So you can stop depression,
but your mind won't listen to you
because you'll be talking to a star.
The mind is already booked up.
You think you already heard it
go by, and the same is true in
meditation.
You can meditate and you are
concentrating on the lama's face,
and the camp's eyes are full of love,
and after a while, your camp's
face looks like a hamburger. Harley,
being hungry? No, no, no, not a
hamburger. I'm a
vegetarian, but that's too late.
This afternoon we said that
you should plant your meditation seeds in the week before,
and it's exactly the same
with this disturbing thought. The main
aspect of stopping it is that
you don't bother other people.
And my name is the two lakes,
these wheels in front. At the
moment, it's very calm, and when
the wind comes up, it will be very
turbulent. And my lover said
every person's mind is like a lake;
when they get agitated, then a mind is
moved, then a lake is so moved, or
they will say something, and then my lake will be
moved. So,
they will disturb mine.
So, if you feel
and have strange thoughts, then it's important not to
disturb other people's minds. So, for
example, you can go for a walk and
not talk to them during that time.  Don't talk to someone else
because you would disturb the lake,
and if you are careful and do
n't disturb other people, then plant the
seeds so that your own is very peaceful.
But it makes no sense to argue
with the seeds at this moment;
it's too late.
It's like pushing a tree back into the ground.
So don't be too serious, and above all, don't get
angry. That doesn't make you
happy. Another question:
this isn't working. Try again.
My question refers to one from
this afternoon, namely
Ronit's. I am the listener of my
thoughts, and when the thoughts, when the
seed opens and the thoughts come,
these seeds make themselves known to the listener. There is
a big debate about this.
Some say it's called a logo, and
luck means a direct cause, and good
means an indirect cause.
Technically frozen, the seed,
so to speak, creates sensory perception, and in
the next millisecond, one becomes
aware of one's mind. First,
the seed creates an object in thought,
and then there is a perception of the
thought, and then comes the feeling. I
think  Technically speaking,
these things happen at different moments,
but you can say that loneliness opened up
in two different ways, namely the
thought and the listener. Technically
speaking, where 1 and 3, namely the first
must carry the second, and then the
third, and this happens at three slightly
different moments.
So what I mean is that the theme
created an object, and the object
created a perception, and the
perception triggered the feeling for me. And
they all came, technically
speaking, from the same seed, but at very slightly
different times.
And that's a big question in the mind
school. But the fourth chamber is something else entirely
because it will be on the
cover. The cover sees what
triggers the next life. For example, in the Wheel
of Life, a Mayan, someone who has
seen the teachers, can't project
new ones.
Someone who has seen the teachers can't
create a new Kramer to find
themselves in suffering again.
But it's possible that they still
have old ladies lying around, up to seven
lives, up
to seven lives. Now we'll do the
book, and tomorrow...  Let's ask more questions
and your questions will get better and better.
Now we're at the third law
of the cover: if you don't do anything,
then you can't
expect a result. And the fourth law is confusing.
This is it again: if you
do something, then you must also get a result.
And some books swap three
and four just so
you don't understand.
In Tibetan, there's a concept called "
Grau," which is a large
metal box, about this size. Inside
is a little brother.
And every person has a Gau a day. When
you become a person, you're given
a Gau, and inside is a little
brother, and you're supposed to keep it for your whole
life. And my Grauer has many
funny stories. For example, when I tried to escape,
they wanted to take him away from me. They thought
I was trying to get out of the country,
and you're supposed to keep him.
Tibetans believe that it can also
stop a bullet.
If someone shoots, it can
stop a bullet. So
the Gau is like a shield.
So, in my example,
sometimes there's a war, and war
in  In Tibet, if someone says there's
a war in Tibet, then
actually only three people were injured.
Some people say, "I
forgot to bring my god to the war," and the
enemy shot many people,
but nothing, nothing, nothing was
touched, even without the mainga, which here
means shopping and, so to speak,
protection from weapons
[Music].
And then they are very surprised,
nothing more, nothing happened, and then
the lama says, "That's not a big
story,
that's simply the third law:
you simply didn't do that to get
an early one." It's
possible, like the woman who walked away from the
crashed plane
and was called injured, everyone died.
I'll tell you a story: I was
in my plane, and I often traveled
with my lama to India to visit the
monasteries.
I always waited until he
had time to go with me because I
thought if I sat in a plane with my lama,
then it would never
crash.
And one day we flew to India.
I sat by the window, and he was in the
other.  I read the newspaper
last night. There was a bomb on the plane,
a small bomb under a seat, and it went
off.
A man fell out of the plane.
Some people are against the war and
nothing happens to them. There's someone in
America, a very famous sniper, who
killed bad people, like
other snipers,
never knowing what would happen. Then he came home
and someone shot him.
It's a true story.
You come home from the war,
nothing happened to you, and then at home
you die in a car accident. Then
some people say his [body part] just stopped
working.
And then the lama says, no, that's not
the reason, that's not the problem, that's not what
happened.
If you think that the [body part] stopped working,
then you don't understand [body part].
When he was at war, he [body part] came [body part], and when
he came home
he [body part], [body part], because [body part], [body part]
again, [body part], something again. If
you do something, then you have to expect a result.
A person, a person who
has the corresponding [body part], can [body part] at [house part].  It's a
house,
and if it burns down, it's possible that
nothing will happen to the person.
Then there's a story in the
old texts about a person who was
half-Ticker, and he was in the same
room as his mother. When it burned down, the
mother died, and nothing happened to him
because he didn't have the karma yet. It
's the same story as the one who
stole the golden elephants.
He simply didn't have the karma
to have the elephants.
Then he talks about a king, who,
sadly,
had a queen,
and she had already
seen most of them directly after she died. She did
n't have to return to the realm of desire,
and she had 500 servants. She taught them all
about Leerhaid,
and they all saw Leerhaid directly.
Then someone set the palace
on fire, and then they
flew around the world, but they could
n't fly far enough. Then
the queen said,
and then the queen said to the sentence, "
We didn't come to that, even
though we are,"
and when everyone fell into the fire,
like Marie Potter's...  So, butterflies,
and then they're related,
and then there was also a dishwasher
in the palace, and she had a hunchback,
and she didn't know anything about emptiness, but
still, she had it. You can't be related, and
then she hid in a big
pipe and escaped.
500 and 501 Aria died, and an
older lady who didn't have the cover
survived.
There was a king of the animals, Dakar. His
famous story is when the village of the
lotto or was attacked. There were
77,000 people in the village, the
majority of whom saw it directly, and every single one
of them was killed.
Some got away, a
few who didn't have this cover,
and that's a long story.
There was a shutter person named Ming
Cheng, and he asked this king who was
killing everyone, "Here's a look.
I'll hold my head underwater,
and as long as my head is underwater,
can you promise that you won't
kill anyone for that long?"
And then the other king said, "Yes, that
's okay." For
30 seconds, he was also a Mayan, and he
held his head underwater.
Then he found his leg down in the
path and then he died,
but he couldn't get up again.
Three hours later, the king said, "Where
is he?" During those three hours,
many others were able to escape,
which means they had... You ca
n't...
And then there's a town called HSV
Wacker, and there's a famous
story about it being covered by a
mudslide,
but two people were able to escape.
These were very
loving people, but the others were
murdered and killed. That's
part of the story of the Wheel of
Life. And if you want to hear the whole story,
then you can
come to Indonesia in August. There's
a beautiful temple there
that was carved into a mountain. It
's a mandala, and it's carved into an
entire mountain. There
are 3,000 carvings there,
roughly the size of that wall over there.
The United Nations
asked me to go there.
It was originally covered by a volcano,
and we're now raising money
for it. There are
many pictures of...  The
Wheel of Life, but they did
n't know that at all, and I told my friends in
Singapore and Indonesia
I'm going there and
giving lectures for two days, and then we'll
provide the money so
that this day can be cleared
of the volcanic soil. Then, if you
have time, you can come there; it
's a wonderful place. We'll
stay in a five-star hotel right next door,
and then there will be two days of lectures
about the Wheel of Life. And this
story comes from the Wheel of
Life.
For me, the third law of
cadre is that if we put this into the void,
for me it's about
expectations, like, "
I
applied for this job, I hope I
get it," or "I called my friend in the
industry, and I hope he can
help me." But they can't
deal with expectations; they're really only about
names. If you don't sow the seed,
then don't get angry if you don't
receive. If you truly
stand, then you don't have to get
angry or wonder if you don't
receive.  If nothing happens, then
you haven't warned anyone. People
always ask me, Kessler.
I actually expected
my friend to help me, and now my
business is in trouble.
And then I ask here, "Have you taken the necessary steps?"
No, but I still
want the result.
No, disappear.
If you don't do the one for city dwellers,
then you shouldn't expect anything.
If you hope for something and
nothing happens, then it's a flaw
in this system.
My husband doesn't give me hugs,
and my wife doesn't give me any. He's
already a problem. A flaw.
You have to see the warm lakes, and if you
understand the third law of the cover,
then you can't blame other people.
If you really don't understand anyone, then
you're never angry at others.
Someone asked me about your stand.
Okay, that I get angry at myself?
No, but it's still Euro Scholz.
Now, the law chamber happened. In
detail, let's say if you blow the seed,
then you must also receive the result.
But the old books formulate it
somewhat differently.
They say if you sow the seed,
then it will never be easy.  So,
going away from oneself, there are some people who were
my diamonds of summer. I was
actually just waiting for those who give
their animals milk to leave, but they
are in another department and I
have no control over that.
Okay, then I just think I'll wait until the
chamber runs out. But
after you've planted a cover,
it won't just go away, and no
matter how long you wait, the
karma has to unfold.
The fourth principle for unfolding, the
chaos, is—we'll get to that later—
for the seeds, that came in your way. They
are stronger than your bodies; they don't
need a body to live.
This body can die
because if Michael were to die now,
if I were to fall over now, then
the seeds would stay here all
alone without a body. They don't need a
body to survive.
Then they open up and then they create
a new world and a new Michael.
Everything you do will come back to you.
We have decided that this
is the third law of presumption: every action
has an equal and opposite
reaction, and there are no exceptions. And
in Buddhism, we don't believe that you
order an exception.  You can mess up the
universe,
it would
mess up this match of the universe.
If you do good things, then you get good
things; if you do bad things, then
you have to get bad things. In
my high school, for example, the mother could write a doctor's note saying she had a headache last night and couldn't do her homework, and that's how it was in my school.  that the
teacher had to accept that,
but my mother never wrote me anything like that.
My mother was like the fourth
strange law. Mom, could I
maybe get an exception letter?
No, you always get what you deserve.
If someone could mess around with it,
then the universe wouldn't be
balanced.
You have to get what you've done. So
why do we have the four forces to
stop the seeds?
Who wants to give me an answer to that?
Is it really true that the four forces
prevent the seeds from
germinating? No,
in Buddhism we have four forces, a kind of confession.
We say that it
stops the seeds, but it's not exactly
correct. If you have a watermelon,
I have one in my
garden. I keep it outside.
I have it in a paper envelope,
and that's okay to
keep it outside because it does
n't rain, and recently it looked like it was raining.
I think the rain came from
Mexico. In my three years of operation,
we've become so sensitive. We
could even feel the salt water in the air from the
Gulf of Mexico.  So,
I definitely wanted to say that
all the warm ones got wet,
and then, so to speak, the message came that
it was time to open, and
then we went out in
the paper envelope and
died because of it, because the whole thing has no earth in
Buddhism.
If you make a good confession, let's call it
the powers, then it will cause the seed to
open too early,
and if you were actually supposed to have a car accident, then now
you only have
a headache. Every seed will
open,
but what you're doing is trying to
open it too early.
But for those of you, the three teachers,
but it doesn't say, like law number
four, that every seed must open.
Technically speaking,
technically speaking, it happened. La
Cava law, a lonely one will
survive for millions of years, and it won't get any less open.
Now we have seven minutes left, and
Kessler, we're wondering why you don't stop. A win, tired,
and my lover,
he once said, "I won't do that." He
had my car accident
before I met him, and he
speaks like Star Wars: "
First, I won't do it." We'll do it as long as it's the
best class.  Rum, the karma of
living beings, the seeds of living beings,
millions of years can pass and
they won't be one percent less
potent. The causes come together,
then the result will appear.
There's no set date for
chemical seeds, no matter how time
passes, they
survive 100 percent and they do
n't just disappear.
Even the smallest cell will
survive for millions of years.
So you're driving in your car and then
you text someone,
then you forget it 50 or 30 seconds
later, but you never forget it. You
've planted a seed.
I heard a wonderful lecture from
a Buddhist nun who made people
laugh. You got
divorced before you even started working, and you still
remember all the
stupid things your husband said, and
you think about it all the time. And he had to
forget on the same day he
said it, right?
But never forget anything.
I have four more minutes, so listen to
the best story. So that you get your
share, sweet dreams, do you have that,
please?  This
is a special cake, this one on
Kauai, so it's a cow patty. It took me quite a
while to
find this photo,
so about 3000 years ago. No, so
I'll start again differently. In the time of [Brother], when
he became very famous,
many people came to him and said, "
I want to become a human,"
and then there were simply too many people.
And then he trained one of his students,
namely Montali Galliano. Montali
Ariana, so you sit outside by the door,
and when people come and say, "I
want to be a student of Brother [Brother], I
want to become a monk,"
then you read their thoughts, who has, so to speak,
clairvoyance, and
then you develop their spirit. So if
you see that they have the [human], the
teachers, the directors, then you can let them choose.
If they don't have the [human],
then in a friendly way, you tell
them that they should leave. And
then Brother [Brother] can, of course,
see everything at any time. The
body check of Montali's spirits, while
common Koreans [swindle money from] people.  Sparkling
wine and then came from a very old,
dirty pharmaceutical company, and his name
was Schreter, and he's very famous.
Oh, that's the one someone
wanted to teach Grandma about December, and then he
learned novels, and then he
forgot about reproduction, and if he
remembered for ten years, then he probably never
forgot. The
mistake was that, and then my whining
read his thoughts and said, "
Go on, that's impossible," and
Butter said, "Wait, wait, wait, what about the
Rhine?"
And then there were, yes, say no, no, yes,
I said he has no
seeds at all, or wait, yes, yes, yes, sometimes
very far away, a mile under the
earth, there are sometimes diamonds, yes, yes,
he's lonely, and then there was,
yes, he says, then how, what, and where he woke,
then life happens, he was born as a fly,
and then he demanded on a cowpat, "
Should you
tell each other another joke?" There's another one, though. A
person will fly over these two,
and they're sitting on dog [ __ ] and
eating, and then one fly says to
a Mainz resident, "Possible for insects."
To become a brother, yes, yes,
we say we have or seeds
in us, yes, yes, and then his brother said why
become a brother, there's
no dog [ __ ] in heaven,
another story,
but this lie, this landed on the foot of the shop,
and then there was a
huge rainstorm, and this
cowpat, which was already a little bit
dried, and the rainstorm, it
washed the cowpat away, and when it came past
a stripper,
this lie, she's sitting on top of it and holding on tight,
he's also riding on the course, and
then there's a stupa and a cage around
the bend, and then the cowpat goes,
the cowpat goes three times around the superman,
if you drive around the superman, then you
get a little good karma, and
many lives later he became
this person, and he said yes, yes,
he has a warm one, he has
the cowpat seed, and he
actually played the teacher, saw
directly, can happen to anyone,
that's a good, good sign,
then we will  Stop it,
and if he really wants it, there wo
n't be water, but there will be dog [ __ ] in heaven.